[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these essential nutrients is present naturally in milk?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Selenium", "Riboflavin", "Biotin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Guillermo del Toro directed both Blade II and Blade Trinity.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What singer and actress starred in the 1981 comedy movie Arthur?", "correct_answer": "Liza Minnelli", "incorrect_answers": ["Madonna", "Barbra Streisand", "Cher"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do historians call the period of 1730-1759 in American history?", "correct_answer": "The Great Awakening", "incorrect_answers": ["The Primitive Era", "The Puritan Era", "The Era of Good Feelings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nickname has been given to the U.S. state of Oregon?", "correct_answer": "Beaver State", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Marmot State", "Otter State"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What problem does Lorraine have in Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Alcoholic", "incorrect_answers": ["Chain smoker", "Unfaithful", "Habitual liar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Europe is the smallest continent.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What celebrated action movie made actor Bruce Willis world famous?", "correct_answer": "Die Hard", "incorrect_answers": ["The Last Boy Scout", "In Country", "Pulp Fiction"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning the word which stands for fox in many languages?", "correct_answer": "Tail", "incorrect_answers": ["Fur", "Nose", "Cunning"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actress, better known as Chloe on the TV show 24,  plays the helpful Pageant  Assistant, Pam, in Little Miss Sunshine.", "correct_answer": "Mary Lynn Rajskub", "incorrect_answers": ["Kirsten Dunst", "Claire Danes", "Amalia Geiheimer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Doctors dont believe that growing causes pain, so growing pains do not exist.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Find the correct statement.", "correct_answer": "Irrupt means  to break in or rush in.", "incorrect_answers": ["Irrupt means to break up.", "Irrupt is not a real English word.", "Irrupt means to come before."]}]